BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Code 5716: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers No. 824/Verizon Florida Inc., 2002-2005 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  8/4/2002-7/30/2005. 2 of 2.
- Code 5719: CWA/GTE Southwest Incorporated, 1995-2001 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  8/16/1995-8/15/1998 and 8/19/1998- 8/15/2001
- Code 5721: CWA/GTE California Incorporated, 1986-2002 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  3/5/86-3/4/89, 3/5/89-12/17/92, 3/18/96- 3/13/99, 3/14/99-3/16/02
- Code 5727: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/Ameritech, 1995-2004 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  6/25/95-6/27/98 and 6/28/98-6/26/04; 1 of 3
- Code 5727: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/Ameritech, 1998-2003 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  6/28/1998- 6/28/2003; 2 of 3
- Code 5727: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/Ameritech, 1998-2003 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  6/28/1998- 6/28/2003 (duplicates); 3 of 3
- Code 5732: CWA District 4/Ameritech, 1995-2001 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  8/6/1995-8/8/1998 and 8/9/1998-3/31/2001; 1 of 2
- Code 5732: CWA District 4/Ameritech, 2001-2004 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  2/1/2001-4/3/2004; 2 of 2
- Code 5734: CWA/Qwest Corporation, 1998-2003 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  8/16/1998-8/16/2003; 1 of 2
- Code 5734: CWA/Qwest Corporation, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  8/17/2003-8/13/2005; 2 of 2
- Code 5736: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/New England Telephone and Telegraph Company, 1994-2000 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  8/5/1994-8/8/1998 and 8/9/1998-8/5/2000; 1 of 2
- Code 5736: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/New England Telephone and Telegraph Company, 1991-1995 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  9/12/1991-8/5/1995; 2 of 2
- Code 5738: CWA No. 1400/New England Telephone Company, 1998-2000 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  8/9/1998-8/5/2000
- Code 5740: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers No. 827/New Jersey Bell/Bell Atlantic-New Jersey Inc., 1992-2002 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  8/9/92-8/5/95, 5/21/95-8/5/00 and 10/9/98-8/10/02
- Code 5741: CWA/Bell Atlantic-New Jersey Inc., 1995-2000 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  8/6/1995-8/8/1998 and 8/9/1998- 8/5/2000
- Code 5744: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers No. 2213/New York Telephone Company, 1986-2000 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  8/10/86-8/89, 12/4/89-8/92, 9/1/91-8/5/95, 4/3/94-8/8/98, 8/9/98-8/5/00
- Code 5746: CWA/New York Telephone Company/Verizon New York Inc., 1994-2003 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  AFL-CIO District 1, Local 1105. 4/3/94-8/8/98, 8/9/98-8/5/00, 8/6/00-8/2/03
- Code 5748: CWA/New York Telephone Company/Verizon New York Inc., 1998-2003 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  AFL-CIO District 1, Local 1110. 8/9/98-8/5/00 and 8/6/00-8/2/03
- Code 5749: CWA/New York Telephone Company, 1989-1998 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  12/4/89-8/92, 9/1/91-8/5/95, 4/3/94- 8/8/98; 1 of 2
- Code 5749: CWA/New York Telephone Company/Verizon New York Inc., 1998-2003 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  8/9/98-8/5/00 and 8/6/00-8/2/03; 2 of 2
- Code 5752: CWA/Pacific Bell/Nevada Bell, 1992-1995 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  8/9/92-8/5/95; 1 of 4
- Code 5752: CWA/Pacific Bell/Nevada Bell, 1995-1998 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  8/6/1995-8/8/1998; 2 of 4
- Code 5752: CWA/Pacific Bell/Nevada Bell, 1998-2001 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  4/1/1998-4/1/2001; 3 of 4
- Code 5752: CWA/Pacific Bell/Nevada Bell, 2001-2004 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  2/5/2001-4/1/2004; 4 of 4
- Code 5763: CWA/BellSouth, 1998-2001 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  8/9/1998-8/4/2001
- Code 5764: Connecticut Union of Telephone Workers/Southern New England Telecommunications Inc., 1981-1989 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  8/1983-8/1986, 11/1986-9/1989; 1 of 4
- Code 5764: Connecticut Union of Telephone Workers/Southern New England Telecommunications Inc., 1992-1998 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  8/8/1992-8/5/1995 and 3/31/1995-8/8/1998; 2 of 4
- Code 5764: Connecticut Union of Telephone Workers/CWA/Southern New England Telecommunications, 1998-2004 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  CWA Local 1298. 9/18/98-4/1/01 and 2/1/01-4/3/04; 3 of 4
- Code 5764: CWA/Southern New England Telecommunications, 2001-2004 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  2/1/01/-4/3/04 (duplicate); 4 of 4
- Code 5765: CWA/Southwestern Bell, 1992-2009 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  8/9/92-8/5/95, 8/6/95-8/8/98, 4/5/98-4/1/01, 2/1/01- 4/3/04 and 4/4/04-4/4/09
- Code 5770: I.B.E.W. No. 89/GTE Northwest Incorporated, 1993-2002 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  5/30/93-5/25/96, 5/26/96- 5/22/99 and 5/23/99-5/18/02
- Code 5778: CWA/Western Union Financial Services, 1990-2000 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  8/7/90-8/6/92, 8/7/92-8/6/94 (memo only), 8/7/94-8/6/97, 8/7/97-8/6/00 (with duplicate)
- Code 5779: NABET/ABC, 1989-1997 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  1989-4/26/1993 and 1993-3/31/1997; 1 of 2
- Code 5779: NABET/ABC, 1997-2003 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  with duplicate
- Code 5780: IBEW/CBS, 1995-2003 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  2/8/1995-6/30/1997, 7/1/1997-7/31/1999 and 8/1/1999- 7/31/2003; 1 of 2
- Code 5780: IBEW/CBS, 2003-2007 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  8/1/03-7/31/07; 2 of 2
- Code 5782: NABET/NBC, 1990-1999 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  6/20/90-3/31/94 and 3/31/94-3/31/99; 1 of 2
- Code 5782: NABET/NBC, 1999-2002 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  4/1/99-3/31/02; 2 of 2
- Code 5798: IBEW No. 1357/GTE Hawaiian Tel, 1991-2002 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  9/23/91-4/30/94, 9/1/96-8/31/99, 9/1/99- 8/31/02
- Code 5799: IBEW No. 723/GTE/Verizon North Inc., 1988-2003 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  12/4/88-11/91, 12/8/91-11/19/94, 2/12/95-11/15/97, 11/16/97-11/11/00 and 1/21/01-11/8/03
- Code 5801: CWA/Carolina Telephone and Telegraph Company, 1999-2005 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  11/30/99-11/29/02 and 11/30/02-11/29/05
- Code 5805: IBEW No. 199/Sprint-Florida Inc., 1998-2001 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  11/13/98-6/30/01
- Code 6000: IBEW/Alabama Power Company, 1995-2001 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  8/14/95-8/15/98 and 8/15/98-8/15/01
- Code 6001: IBEW No. 387/Arizona Public Service Company, 1987-2002 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  4/1/87-3/90, 4/1/90-4/1/93, 4/1/93-4/1/95, 4/1/95-4/1/97, 4/1/97-4/1/99 and 4/1/99-4/1/02
- Code 6007: Utility Workers Union of America No. 270/Cleveland Electric/FirstEnergy Corp., 1988-2000 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  5/1/88-4/90, 5/1/91-5/1/93, 5/1/93-5/1/97 and 5/27/98-4/30/00
- Code 6008: IBEW No. 15/Commonwealth Edison Company, 1995-2003 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  4/1/95-9/30/97 and 8/25/97- 3/31/01
- Code 6012: IBEW/Diquesne Light Company, 1987-2003 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  10/1/87-9/90, 10/1/90-9/30/93, 10/31/96- 9/30/01 and 9/30/01-9/30/03
- Code 6013: IBEW/Florida Power Corp., 1999-2002 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  12/6/99-12/1/02
- Code 6014: IBEW/Florida Power and Light Co., 1988-2000 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  11/1/88-10/31/91, 11/1/91-10/31/94, 11/1/94-10/31/97 and 11/1/97-10/31/00
- Code 6015: IBEW No. 84/Georgia Power Co., 1990-2002 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  7/1/90-6/30/93, 7/1/93-6/30/96, 7/1/96- 6/30/99 and 7/1/99-6/30/02
- Code 6016: IBEW No. 66/Houston Lighting and Power Company/Reliant Energy/CenterPoint Energy, 1990-2006 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  5/26/90-5/25/93, 5/26/93-5/25/95, 5/26/95-5/25/98, 5/26/98-5/25/00, 5/26/00-5/25/03 and 5/26/03-5/25/06
- Code 6017: IBEW No. 84/Georgia Power, 2002-2005 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  7/1/02-6/30/05
- Code 6018: Gas Workers No. 80/Michigan Consolidated Gas Company, 1994-2004 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  12/4/94-12/7/97, 12/7/97-12/3/00 and 12/3/00-12/2/04
- Code 6025: IBEW No. 1600/Pennsylvania Power and Light Company, 1988-2002 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  7/25/88-7/21/91, 7/22/91-5/22/94, 5/23/94-5/18/97 and 5/18/98-5/12/02
- Code 6026: IBEW No. 1900/Potomac Electric Power Company, 1990-2004 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  11/19/1990-5/31/93, 6/1/93-5/31/96, 1/24/99-5/31/03 and 5/31/03-5/31/04
- Code 6027: IBEW/Public Service Electric and Gas Company, 1980-1984 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Code 6027: IBEW/Public Service Electric and Gas Company, 1972-2002 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  2/15/1972, 5/1/1980- 4/30/1982, 5/1/1989-4/30/1992, 5/1/1996-4/30/2002; 2 of 2
- Code 6029: IBEW No. 77/Puget Sound Power and Light Company, 1989-2002 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  12/20/89-3/31/93, 3/12/91-3/31/94, 4/1/94-3/31/97, 4/1/97-4/1/99 and 4/1/99-3/31/02
- Code 6030: IBEW No. 47/Southern California Edison Company, 2001-2003 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  1/1/01-12/31/03
- Code 6036: International Union of Operating Engineers No. 148/Union Electric Company, 1990-2007 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  7/1/90-7/1/93, 7/1/93-7/1/96, 7/1/96-7/1/99, 7/1/99-7/1/02, 6/30/02-6/30/03 and 7/1/03-7/1/07
- Code 6039: Utility Workers of America No. 102/West Penn Power/Allegheny Power Service, 1989-2001 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  5/1/89-4/30/92, 5/1/92-4/30/95, 5/1/96-5/1/99, 10/22/97-4/30/2001
- Code 6040: IBEW No. 2150/Wisconsin Electric Power Company, 1998-2004 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  9/11/98-8/15/01 and 8/23/01-8/15/04
- Code 6043: Transport Workers Union No. 101/Brooklyn Union Gas, 1986-1998 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  10/15/86-10/15/89 and 10/16/95-10/15/98; 1 of 2
- Code 6043: Transport Workers Union No. 101/Brooklyn Union Gas, 1998-2001 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  10/16/98-10/15/01; 2 of 2
- Code 6044: Natural Gas Workers Union No. 555/East Ohio Gas, 1991-2006 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  6/16/91-6/15/94, 6/16/94- 6/15/97, 6/16/97-6/15/01 and 6/16/01-6/15/06
- Code 6045: United Gas Workers Union No. 69/Dominion Transmission/Hope Gas Inc., 1998-2005 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  12/11/98-4/1/02 and 4/1/02-4/1/05
- Code 6047: Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union No. 5-6/Laclede Gas Company, 1991-2004 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  8/1/91-7/31/94, 8/1/94-7/31/97, 8/1/97-7/31/00 and 8/1/00-7/31/04
- Code 6050: Utility Workers Union/International Chemical Workers Union/Southern California Gas Company, 1988-1993 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  4/1/88-3/31/91 and 6/1/91-3/31/93; 1 of 2
- Code 6050: Utility Workers Union/International Chemical Workers Union/Southern California Gas Company, 1996-2002 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  9/9/96-3/31/00 and 4/1/00-3/31/02; 2 of 2
- Code 6054: Teamsters No. 96/International Union of Gas Workers/Washington Gas Light Company, 1989-2000 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  6/1/89-6/1/92, 6/1/92-6/1/95 and 12/12/97-6/1/00
- Code 6055: IBEW No. 1347/Cincinnati Gas and Electric Company, 1988-2001 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  4/1/88-4/1/91, 4/1/91- 4/1/94, 4/1/94-4/1/97 and 10/14/96-4/1/01
- Code 6056: Independent Utilities Union/Cincinnati Gas and Electric Company, 1989-2002 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  3/22/89- 3/22/92, 3/22/92-3/22/98, 11/11/96-4/1/02
- Code 6057: IBEW No. 420 and 457/Connecticut Light and Power Company, 1995-2009 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  6/1/95- 6/1/98, 6/1/98-6/1/01, 6/1/01-6/1/04, 6/1/04-6/1/09
- Code 6058: Utility Workers Union of America No. 1-2/Consolidated Edison Company, 1973-2000 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  4/1/73-4/30/75, 3/2/75-6/17/77, 6/18/77-6/17/80, 6/18/80-6/17/83, 8/21/83-6/17/86, 6/15/86-6/24/89, 6/21/92-6/22/96, 6/23/96-6/24/00
- Code 6059: Utility Workers of America/Consumers Power Company, 1971-1983 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  9/1/71-9/1/74, 9/1/74-9/1/77, 9/1/77-9/1/80 and 9/1/80-9/1/83; 1 of 2
- Code 6059: Utility Workers of America/Consumers Power Company, 1983-2000 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  Michigan State Utility Workers Council; 9/1/83-9/1/86, 9/1/86-9/1/89, 6/1/89-6/1/92, 6/1/92-6/1/95 and 6/1/95-6/1/00; 2 of 2
- Code 6060: UWUA No. 175/Dayton Power and Light Company, 1989-1999 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  11/1/89-10/31/93 and 11/1/93-10/31/99
- Code 6061: UWUA No. 223/Detroit Edison Company, 1993-1999 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  6/10/93-6/5/95 and 6/5/95- 6/7/99
- Code 6063: IBEW No. 51/Illinois Power Company, 1984-2003 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  7/1/1984-6/30/1986, 7/1/1986- 6/30/1988, 8/16/1988-6/30/1991, 7/4/1991-6/30/1994, 5/6/1995-6/30/1998, 5/6/1998-6/30/2003
- Code 6064: IBEW/Jersey Central Power and Light Company, 1991-1999 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  11/1/1991-10/31/1994, 11/1/1994-10/31/1996, 11/1/1996-10/31/1999
- Code 6065: IBEW No. 1049/Long Island Lighting Company, 1985-2001 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  10/1/85-2/89, 2/14/89- 2/13/92, 2/14/92-2/13/96, 2/14/96-2/13/01
- Code 6066: IBEW No. 1381/Long Island Lighting Company, 1984-2001 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  8/14/1984-2/13/1986, 10/1/1985-2/13/1989, 2/14/1989-2/13/1992, 2/14/1992-2/13/1996, 2/14/1996-2/13/2001
- Code 6068: IBEW/Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation, 1984-2001 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  Local 97; 6/1/84-5/86, 6/1/86- 5/89, 6/1/90-5/31/93, 6/1/93-2/29/96, 3/1/1996-5/31/01
- Code 6069: USWA No. 12775/Northern Indiana Public Service Company, 1993-2004 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  6/1/93-5/31/97, 6/1/97-5/31/99 and 6/1/99-5/31/04
- Code 6070: IBEW/New York State Electric and Gas Corporation, 1995-2000 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  7/1/95-6/30/97 and 7/1/97-6/30/00
- Code 6071: IBEW No. 1245/Pacific Gas and Electric Company, 1994-2002 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  1/1/94-12/31/97, 1/1/97- 12/31/99 and 1/1/00-12/31/02
- Code 6072: IBEW No. 1245/Pacific Gas and Electric Company, 1994-2002 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Code 6073: Engineers and Scientists of California No. 20/Pacific Gas and Electric Company, 1994-2002 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  1/1/94-12/31/97, 1/1/97-12/31/99 and 1/1/00-12/31/02
- Code 6074: Gas Workers Union No. 18007/Peoples Gas Light and Coke Company, 1991-2002 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  5/10/91-4/30/94, 5/13/94-4/30/98, 5/15/98-4/30/01
- Code 6075: IBEW No. 111/Public Service Company of Colorado, 1997-2006 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  6/1/97-5/31/00, 6/1/00- 5/31/03 and 6/1/03-5/31/06
- Code 6076: Utility Co-Workers Association/Public Service Electric and Gas Company, 1996-2002 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  5/1/96-4/30/02
- Code 6077: IBEW No. 465/San Diego Gas and Electric Company, 1996-2001 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  3/1/96-8/31/98 and 9/1/98-8/31/01
- Code 6079: IBEW/Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1988-2002 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  4/18/88-3/31/89, 4/4/89-3/31/92, 6/5/92-3/31/95, 5/2/95-3/31/98, 4/1/98-3/31/00 (extension) and 3/3/00-3/31/02
- Code 6080: IBEW No. 965/Wisconsin Power and Light Company, 1996-2003 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  6/1/96-5/31/99 and 6/1/99-6/1/03
- Code 6081: International Union of Operating Engineers No. 310/Wisconsin Public Service Corporation, 1994-2003 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  10/29/94-10/28/97, 4/24/98-10/28/00 and 10/29/00-10/25/03
- Code 6082: Teamsters No. 731, 1998-2003 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  Excavating, Grading, Asphalt, Private Scavengers, Automobile Salesroom Garage Attendants, Linen and Laundry Union; 10/1/98-9/30/03
- Code 6084: IBEW/Northern Illinois Gas Company/Nicor Gas, 1988-2000 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  2/1/88-1/31/91, 2/1/91- 1/31/94 (production and clerical), 2/1/94-2/28/97 (production and clerical), 3/1/97-2/29/00; 1 of 2
- Code 6084: IBEW No. 19/Nicor Gas, 2000-2004 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  3/1/2000-2/28/2003 and 3/1/2003-2/29/2004; 2 of 2
- Code 6089: IBEW No. 320 and 2218/Central Hudson, 1998-2003 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  7/1/98-4/30/03
- Code 6093: IBEW No. 108/Tampa Electric, 1995-2004 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  1/30/95-3/31/98, 3/23/98-3/31/01 and 4/16/01- 3/31/04
- Code 6094: Utility Workers Union No. 246/Southern California Edison, 1995-2000 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  1/1/95-12/31/98 and 1/1/99-12/31/00; 1 of 3
- Code 6094: UWUA No. 246/Southern California Edison, 2001-2003 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  1/1/01-12/31/03; 2 of 3
- Code 6094: UWUA No. 246/Southern California Edison, 2004-2008 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  1/1/04-6/30/08 (volume 1 and 2 with duplicates); 3 of 3
- Code 6096: IBEW No. 962/Duke Power Company, 2001-2003 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  10/1/01-10/1/02 and 10/1/02- 10/1/03
- Code 6105: Gas Works Employees Union of Philadelphia No. 686/Philadelphia Gas Works, 1989-2004 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  5/16/89-5/15/93, 5/16/93-5/10/98, 5/16/98-5/15/01 and 5/16/01-5/15/04
- Code 6106: IBEW/Alabama Power Company, 1995-2001 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Code 6301: UFCW No. 1001/Bon Marche Metro, 1996-2003 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  5/1/96-4/30/00 and 5/1/00-4/30/03
- Code 6309: Teamsters No. 553, 1994-2004 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  1994-1996, 1998-2001, 2001-2004
- Code 6310: Teamsters No. 630/Associated Produce Dealers and Brokers of Los Angeles, 1993-2004 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  2/1/93-1/31/96, 2/1/96-1/31/00 and 7/1/99-1/31/04
- Code 6316: Service Employees International Union No. 1877, 1994-2005 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  1/14/91-1/16/94, 1/20/97- 1/21/01, 1/22/01-1/23/05
- Code 6317: Teamsters No. 282/Lumber Industry, 1999-2005 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  7/1/99-6/30/02 and 7/1/02-6/30/05
- Code 6325: Teamsters No. 786/Northern Illinois Ready Mix and Materials Association, 1995-2000 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  5/1/95-4/30/00
- Code 6331: ILWU/Industrial Employers and Distributors Association, 1994-2007 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  7/7/94-5/31/98, 6/1/98-5/31/03, 7/2/98-5/03, 9/30/03-5/07
- Code 6336: United Food and Commercial Workers Union No. 536/Kroger Co., 1991-1999 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  2/3/91- 2/4/95 and 2/4/95-6/5/99
- Code 6337: UFCW No. 791/Shaw's Supermarkets, 1991-2008 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  7/27/91-7/30/94, 7/31/94-7/27/97, 7/27/97-7/27/01, 2/5/00-12/1/01, 7/28/01-7/31/04, 8/1/04-8/2/08
- Code 6339: UFCW No. 911/Meijer Inc., 1994-2002 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  7/8/94-9/19/98 and 12/7/1998-9/21/02
- Code 6341: UFCW No. 371/Shaw's Supermarkets, 1995-2008 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  10/29/95-2/5/00, 2/5/00-12/1/01 (with duplicate), 2/22/00, 12/2/01-3/6/04, 3/7/04-3/6/08
- Code 6344: UFCW No. 23/Giant Eagle Markets (Grocery), 1994-1999 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  6/26/94-6/27/99
- Code 6345: UFCW No. 23/Giant Eagle Markets (Meat and Deli), 1994-1999 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Code 6352: UFCW No. 655/Schnuck Markets, 1994-2007 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  6/12/94-6/7/97, 6/8/97-6/11/00, 6/12/00- 6/15/03 and 6/16/03-5/13/07
- Code 6354: UFCW No. 546/Dominick's Finer Foods Inc., 1991-1997 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  7/28/91-7/30/94 and 7/31/94- 7/26/97
- Code 6355: UFCW No. 1 and 23/Quality Markets, 1992-2004 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  6/14/92-6/8/96, 6/9/96-6/10/00, 6/11/00-6/7/03 and 6/7/03-4/7/04
- Code 6359: UFCW No. 1496, 1996-2002 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  8/1/96-5/31/99 and 6/1/99-5/31/02
- Code 6361: UFCW No. 27/Acme Markets, 1997-2008 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  4/30/97-4/24/99, 4/25/99-7/19/03 and 7/19/03- 7/19/08
- Code 6362: UFCW No. 1000 and 2/Homeland Stores/HAC, 1996-2007 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  8/4/96-8/4/01, 8/5/01-8/7/04, 9/7/02-10/6/07
- Code 6364: UFCW No. 911/Kroger Grocery Unit, 1996-2007 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  6/30/96-4/1/99, 4/1/99-4/1/03, 4/2/03- 4/7/07
- Code 6365: UFCW No. 1360/Zallie Supermarkets, 1998-2001 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  4/25/98-4/28/01
- Code 6366: Teamsters No. 38/Allied Employers Inc., 1998-2004 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  8/2/98-8/5/01 and 8/6/01- 8/7/04
- Code 6367: UFCW No. 1360/Acme Markets, 1999-2009 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  4/25/99-4/24/04 and 4/25/04-4/25/09
- Code 6370: UFCW No. 464A/Pathmark, 1998-2007 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  12/20/98-4/19/03 and 4/20/03-8/18/07
- Code 6371: UFCW No. 464A/Grand Union/Stop and Shop, 1998-2007 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  12/20/98-4/19/03 and 4/20/03- 8/18/07
- Code 6372: UFCW No. 1996/Kroger Company, 1998-2002 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  4/5/98-4/6/02
- Code 6377: UFCW No. 1500/Edwards Super Food Stores/Stop and Shop, 1998-2006 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  6/21/98-6/22/02 and 6/23/02-6/24/06
- Code 6378: UFCW No. 1500/D'Agostino Supermarkets, 1994-2004 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  6/19/94-6/21/97, 6/22/97-7/29/00, 7/30/00-7/31/04
- Code 6379: UFCW No. 1529/Memphis Meat, 1999-2003 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  10/3/99-10/4/03
- Code 6380: UFCW No. 1529/Memphis Clerks, 1999-2003 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Code 6382: UFCW No. 464A/Stop and Shop, 2000-2008 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  7/16/00-7/17/04 and 7/18/04-11/8/08
- Code 6385: UFCW No. 464A/Stop and Shop, 2003-2007 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  4/20/03-8/18/07
- Code 6386: UFCW No. 135/Food 4 Less, 2000-2004 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  2/27/00-2/28/04
- Code 6500: United Storeworkers No. 3/Bloomingdale's, 1985-1996 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Code 6500: United Storeworkers No. 3/Bloomingdale's, 1996-2000 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Code 6513: UFCW No. 101/Macy's, 1996-2004 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  6/14/96-5/31/99 and 6/1/99-5/31/04
- Code 6513: UFCW No. 1/Tops Market, 2001-2005 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  8/2/01-7/31/05
- Code 6541: UFCW No. 1445/May Company/William Filene's Sons, 1988-2001 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  11/21/88-2/3/91 and 2/2/97-2/4/01
- Code 6547: UFCW No. 400/Hechts, 1995-2005 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  7/20/95-7/19/00 and 7/19/00-7/19/2005
- Code 6571: UFCW No. 1/P&C Foods, 1992-2004 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  5/31/92-6/1/96, 6/2/96-6/2/01, 6/3/01-5/30/04 and 5/30/04-10/6/04
- Code 6580: Department Store Workers Union No. 1-S/Macy's Northeast Inc., 1993-1999 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  August 1994
- Code 6585: Teamsters No. 986/Price Company, 1995-2004 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  2/1/95-2/1/98, 2/1/98-2/1/01, 2/1/01- 2/1/04
- Code 6590: Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees No. 399/NBC Merchants, 1996-2002 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  6/1/96-5/31/99, 6/1/99-5/31/02
- Code 6591: UFCW No. 951/Meijer Great Lakes Limited Partnership, 1999-2008 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Code 6592: UFCW No. 1439/Allied Employers Inc., 1999-2002 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  4/4/99-4/7/02
- Code 6701: UFCW No. 1245/ACME Markets, 1984-2001 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  10/14/84-10/10/87, 10/14/90-10/9/93, 10/10/93-11/8/97, 11/9/97-11/10/01
- Code 6703: UFCW No. 880/Cleveland Food Industry Committee/Akron-Canton Food Industry Committee, 1993-2005 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  9/13/93-9/8/96, 9/8/96-9/12/99, 9/12/99-9/8/02, 9/9/02-9/11/05
- Code 6704: UFCW No. 880/Cleveland Food Industry Committee, 1984-2005 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  9/9/90-9/12/93, 9/13/93-9/8/96, 9/8/96-9/12/99, 9/12/99-9/8/02, 9/9/02-9/11/05
- Code 6706: UFCW No. 371/Edwards Super Food/Stop and Shop Supermarkets, 1993-2004 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  5/9/93- 5/11/96, 5/12/96-5/15/99, 5/16/99-2/10/01, 2/11/01-2/14/04
- Code 6707: UFCW/Food Employers Council, Inc., 1993-1999 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  10/4/93-10/6/96 and 10/2/95- 10/3/99
- Code 6709: UFCW No. 1245/Kings Supermarkets, 1993-2005 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  11/21/1993-11/22/1997, 11/23/1997- 11/24/2001, 11/25/2001-11/19/2005
- Code 6711: UFCW No. 1/Tops Markets, 1996-2001 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  10/13/1996-3/31/2001
- Code 6712: UFCW No. 1/Tops Markets, 1996-2002 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  10/13/1996-4/28/2001
- Code 6714: UFCW No. 1105/Allied Employers Inc., 1995-2004 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  4/30/95-5/3/98, 5/3/98-5/6/01, 5/6/01- 5/2/04
- Code 6715: UFCW No. 381/Allied Employers Inc., 1992-2004 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  5/3/92-4/30/95, 4/30/95-5/3/98/, 5/3/98- 5/6/01, 5/6/01-5/2/04
- Code 6718: Retail, Wholesale and Chain Store Food Employees Union No. 338/Edwards, 1998-2002 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  10/4/98-10/5/02
- Code 6719: Retail, Wholesale and Chain Store Food Employees No. 338, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Code 6725: UFCW No. 464A/The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, 1993-2008 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  4/25/93- 7/27/96, 7/28/96-7/15/00, 7/16/00-7/17/04, 7/18/04-11/8/08
- Code 6726: UFCW No. 27/Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, 1996-2004 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  9/22/96-3/25/00 and 3/26/00-3/27/04
- Code 6727: UFCW No. 464A/ShopRite, 1995-2007 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  1/1/95-12/19/98, 12/20/98-4/19/03, 4/20/03- 8/18/07
- Code 6730: UFCW No. 555/Portland and Vicinity Grocery, Produce and Delicatessen, 1997-2003 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  7/20/97-7/22/00, 7/23/00-7/28/03
- Code 6735: UFCW No. 653, 1960-2004 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Code 6740: UFCW No. 1546/Jewel Food Stores, 1991-2009 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  7/28/91-7/30/94, 7/31/94-7/26/97, 7/27/97-7/26/03, 8/27/04-3/2/09
- Code 6745: UFCW No. 881/Jewel Food Stores, 1989-2005 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  10/1/89-9/26/92, 9/27/92-9/30/95, 10/1/95-10/3/98, 10/4/98-10/6/02, 10/6/02-10/2/05
- Code 6746: UFCW No. 347/Kroger, 1990-2002 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  10/7/90-10/8/94, 10/9/94-10/9/99, 10/10/99- 4/30/02
- Code 6747: UFCW No. 23/Kroger, 1995-2004 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  10/8/95-10/7/00 and 10/8/00-11/6/04
- Code 6748: UFCW No. 1059 and 1099/Kroger, 1995-2000 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  9/17/95-9/16/00
- Code 6749: UFCW No. 1000/Kroger, 1990-1997 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  5/6/90-5/8/93, 5/9/93-5/11/96, 5/11/96-5/10/97
- Code 6752: UFCW No. 1996/Kroger, 1991-2001 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  6/28/91-11/8/97, 11/9/97-11/10/01
- Code 6755: UFCW No. 428/Safeway, 1992-2004 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  3/1/92-3/4/95, 9/7/97-9/1/01, 9/2/01-9/11/04 (with duplicate); 1 of 2
- Code 6755: UFCW No. 428/Safeway, 2001-2007 (Box 39, Folder 22)